[mellow music]
[柔和的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
One large Flotsam fries,
extra Jetsam,
一大块漂浮薯条，
额外的Jetsam，
four orders of duckweed.
四份浮萍。
Hmm.
唔。
Methinks thou forgot my gravy,
我想你忘记了我的肉汁，
thou lumpish clay-brained
flap dragon.
你这个笨蛋
拍打龙。
[laughs]
Flap dragon.
[笑]
拍打龙.
[giggles]
- [sighs]
[咯咯笑]
- [叹气]
Oh, and finally,
哦，最后，
one Deep Sea Donut.
一个深海甜甜圈。
That comes to a total of...
这样一来，总共...
Whatever the measure, squire,
put it on my account.
不管采取什么措施，乡绅，
把它记到我的账户上。
- Oh, no, you don't.
- [gasps]
- 哦，不，你不知道。
- [喘气]
No more food for you
until you pay your tab.
没有更多的食物给你
直到您付清帐单。
[stammering]
Pay tab?
[结巴]
付费标签？
I'll flip you for it.
我会为它翻转你。
[coin jingles]
- I'll take that.
[硬币歌曲]
- 我会接受的。
How about a friendly game
of Three Deadly Challenges?
来场友谊赛怎么样
三个致命的挑战？
[dramatic orchestral music]
[戏剧性管弦乐]
Oh, castle.
Pick castle!
哦，城堡。
选择城堡！
[groans]
[呻吟]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
[laughs]
I bet we'll never see
[笑]
我打赌我们永远不会看到
that game geek again.
又是那个游戏极客。
[bell dings] - 50 Krabby Patties please.
[铃声]- 请给我 50 个蟹黄饼。
Extra pickles!
额外的泡菜！
Put it on my tab.
把它放在我的标签上。
Coming right up.
马上就来了。
- Bubble Bass!
- [whimpers]
- 泡泡鲈鱼！
- [呜咽]
- [snarls]
- [chuckles]
- [咆哮]
- [轻笑]
♪ Hey, nonny-nonny ♪
♪ 嘿，老妈老妈 ♪
♪ You look pretty funny ♪
♪ 你看起来很有趣 ♪
♪ You won't get my money,
nah, nah-nah, nah-nah ♪
♪ 你不会得到我的钱，
不，不，不，不，不 ♪
[car horn honks]
[汽车喇叭鸣响]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
Mr. Squidward!
章鱼哥先生！
I want you and SpongeBob
to go after Bubble Bass,
我想要你和海绵宝宝
去追泡泡鲈鱼，
and collect his tab.
并收集他的标签。
[squeals]
[尖叫声]
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
Hey, nonny-nonny,
you look pretty funny.
嘿，尼尼尼尼，
你看起来很有趣。
You won't get my money. You...
- [sighs]
你不会得到我的钱。你...
- [叹气]
I can't help it.
It's catchy.
我无能为力。
很吸引人。
Look, I just want
to collect the money
你看，我只是想要
收钱
as soon as possible and go.
尽快走吧。
Bubble Bass!
We're here to collect your tab!
泡泡贝斯！
我们来收集您的标签！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Squidward,
that was so masculine.
章鱼哥，
那真是太有男子气概了。
Uh, well, I... [clears throat]
呃，好吧，我...[清嗓子]
Let's go.
我们走吧。
I know you're in here.
Come out.
我知道你在这儿。
出来。
[sniffs]
Smells funny in here.
[嗅嗅]
这里闻起来很奇怪。
Smells like deadbeat.
闻起来像死气沉沉的人。
Hmm.
唔。
If you don't pay up,
如果你不还钱的话
we'll sell this furniture.
我们要卖掉这件家具。
- [gasps]
- Whoops.
- [喘气]
- 哎呀。
How much do you think
this is worth?
你觉得多少
这值得吗？
I just chipped it.
我刚刚把它切碎了。
Oh, it was the chip
that sold me!
哦，原来是芯片
那卖了我！
I'll give you 10 bucks.
- Hey!
我给你10块钱。
- 嘿！
Don't touch mother's things.
I'll pay the tab.
不要碰妈妈的东西。
我来付帐单。
Come downstairs,
and we'll work it out.
下楼来，
我们会解决这个问题的。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[both yelp]
[两人都尖叫]
[crashing]
[崩溃]
[moaning]
[呻吟]
- My savior.
- Huh? Oh.
- 我的救星。
- 啊？哦。
All right, where is he?
好吧，他在哪儿？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
If you want me to pay,
you'll have to play
如果你要我付钱的话
你必须玩
The Three Deadly Challenges.
三个致命的挑战。
Oh!
The Three Deadly Challenges!
哦！
三大致命挑战！
[excited panting]
I've got this game.
[兴奋气喘吁吁]
我有这个游戏。
Where is it? Game of Strife,
Chutes and Bladders...
它在哪里？冲突游戏，
滑槽和气囊...
Oh, here it is!
Ah!
哦，在这里！
啊!
The Three Deadly Challenges.
[dramatic orchestral music]
三个致命的挑战。
[戏剧性管弦乐]
A board game. Whoopee.
一款棋盘游戏。哎呀。
Okay, Bubble Bass.
We accept the challenge.
好吧，泡泡巴斯。
我们接受挑战。
Why are you giving him
the upper hand?
你为什么要给他
占上风？
He owes us money!
他欠我们钱！
Oh.
哦。
But I wanna pway
The Thwee Deadwy Chawwenges.
但我想走
Thwee Deadwy Chawwenges。
Oh, all wight... [clears throat]
噢，好吧……[清嗓子]
All right already!
Let's get this over with.
已经好了！
让我们结束这一切吧。
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊！
[laughs]
[crashes]
[笑]
[崩溃]
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
- Wow!
- Huh?
- 哇！
- 啊？
A life-size version
of the Three Deadly Challenges.
真人大小的版本
三个致命的挑战。
Beautiful!
美丽的！
Looks like a hobo campground.
看起来像一个流浪汉露营地。
No, Squidward.
不，章鱼哥。
You have to look
with your imagination.
你必须看看
凭你的想象力。
What the... oh!
[speaks gibberish]
什么啊……哦！
[胡言乱语]
It's a dump!
这是一个垃圾场！
Thou art two oozing cysts
你是两个渗出的囊肿
on the hindside
of a plague dog's nose.
在后侧
瘟疫狗的鼻子。
What did he say?
他说什么？
The colorful insults
are the best part of the game!
五彩缤纷的辱骂
是游戏中最好的部分！
That figures. Hmm.
这数字。唔。
So how do you win
this goofball game, anyway?
那么你如何获胜
无论如何，这个愚蠢的游戏？
Since Bubble Bass challenged us,
自从 Bubble Bass 向我们发起挑战以来，
all we have to do is get
close enough to tag him out.
我们所要做的就是得到
距离足够近，可以把他标记出来。
We get three chances,
我们有3次机会，
or should I say,
Three Challenges.
或者我应该说，
三大挑战。
- Oh, hmm.
- Oh, boy!
- 哦，嗯。
- 哦，孩子！
Look, Squidward!
[grunting]
看，章鱼哥！
[咕噜声]
Oh, this feels stupid.
哦，这感觉很愚蠢。
[sighs]
[叹气]
both: Charge!
两人：冲锋！
[yelling]
[大喊]
[strains]
[菌株]
Huh?
Uh-oh.
啊？
呃哦。
What?
[both yell]
什么？
[两人大喊]
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
Tag, you lose!
[both laughing]
标签，你输了！
[两人都笑了]
[screams]
We decapitated him!
[尖叫声]
我们把他斩首了！
Oh, calm down.
噢，冷静点。
It's just a dummy made from
his mother's couch cushions
这只是一个假人
他母亲的沙发垫
and a sleeping bag.
[sighs]
和一个睡袋。
[叹气]
All of this for a tab?
所有这些都是为了一个标签？
Oh!
哦！
But you were magnificent, Squidward.
但你很棒，章鱼哥。
So strong and courageous.
如此坚强和勇敢。
As always.
一如既往。
Thy canker sore bottoms
curdle seaweed
你的臀部溃疡
凝结海藻
and sour the ocean.
并使海洋变酸。
- Oh, you...
- I got this one, Squidward.
- 哦，你...
- 我拿到了这个，章鱼哥。
Oh, yeah? Well, your pillows
are filed with urchins,
哦，是吗？嗯，你的枕头
与海胆一起归档，
and your shirts are inside out!
而且你的衬衫反面了！
Adding injury to insult.
侮辱上加伤害。
[trumpet fanfare]
- [groans]
[喇叭声]
- [呻吟]
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
Oh, look at all this junk.
哦，看看这些垃圾。
[excitedly] I know.
Isn't it great?
[兴奋]我知道。
不是很好吗？
[groans]
[呻吟]
Let's finish this.
让我们完成这个吧。
He's obviously in that bullpen.
他显然就在那个牛棚里。
[huffing and growling]
[气喘吁吁]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[roars]
[怒吼]
both: Bubble Bass' mom!
两人：泡泡巴斯的妈妈！
You!
You chipped my furniture!
你！
你把我的家具弄碎了！
[growls]
[咆哮]
He tricked us.
What do we do?
他欺骗了我们。
我们该怎么办？
Hide!
[both whimpering]
隐藏！
[两人都呜咽]
And that's my good tablecloth!
这就是我的好桌布！
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[all grunting and screaming]
[所有的咕哝声和尖叫声]
[quirky music]
[古怪的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ah.
啊。
[both humming]
[两人都哼哼]
[tango music]
[探戈音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Aww!
哇！
[alarm buzzing]
[警报声响起]
- Huh?
- [grunts]
- 啊？
- [咕哝]
Sorry, sweetie.
Gotta run.
对不起，亲爱的。
得跑了。
I'm late for the bake sale.
- [moans]
我参加烘焙义卖迟到了。
- [呻吟]
Call me!
打电话给我！
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Mother!
母亲！
[screaming]
Why?
[尖叫]
为什么？
[ground rumbling]
[地面隆隆声]
Whoa!
哇！
[crowd cheering,
trumpet fanfare]
[人群欢呼，
小号号角]
[strains]
[菌株]
Sir Squidward,
you look magnificent
章鱼哥先生，
你看起来棒极了
upon your mighty steed.
骑在你强大的战马上。
[gasps]
Yes.
[喘气]
是的。
Yes, I see it now!
是的，我现在看到了！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Any last words, Squid-wuss?
最后还有什么话要说吗，鱿鱼乌斯？
May thy fat head
愿你的胖头
be set upon by sea spiders
and torn asunder,
被海蜘蛛袭击
并被撕裂，
leaving only thine eyes
to witness the humiliation!
只留下你的眼睛
见证屈辱！
Ooh, pretty good last words.
呵呵，最后一句话说得好。
Sir Squidward, thy shield.
章鱼哥先生，你的盾牌。
Ha!
Shield, shmield.
哈!
盾牌，施米尔德。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
My hero.
我的英雄。
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
[both growl]
[双方咆哮]
[inhales]
[horn blaring]
[吸气]
[喇叭声]
Ah!
啊!
Ya!
呀！
- Ya!
- Ah, ha-ha!
- 是啊！
- 啊，哈哈！
[roars]
[怒吼]
Oh, I can't look.
哦，我看不下去。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Mommy!
妈妈！
[growling]
[咆哮]
[slowed groaning]
[缓慢的呻吟]
All right, Bubble Bass.
You're tagged.
好吧，泡泡巴斯。
你被标记了。
Pay your tab.
支付你的账单。
[mocking grunts]
[嘲笑的咕哝声]
You bested me
at Three Deadly Challenges.
你打败了我
在三个致命的挑战中。
But I am broke!
但我破产了！
Verily, I spent all of my money
on cardboard.
确实，我的钱都花光了
在纸板上。
What are you going to do to me?
你要对我做什么？
Nothing,
but I am sure Mr. Krabs
没什么，
但我确信蟹老板
has some Deadly Challenges
of his own for you.
有一些致命的挑战
他自己的给你的。
[labored breathing]
[呼吸困难]
This is torture!
这就是折磨！
My arms are killing me.
我的手臂快要死了。
I can't feel my fingers.
我感觉不到我的手指了。
I feel a cramp!
I'm cramped!
我感觉抽筋！
我很局促！
My back is breaking.
我的背快断了。
[wailing]
[哀号]
[moans]
[呻吟声]
[overlapping complaints]
- That guy is terrible!
[重叠投诉]
——那个家伙太可怕了！
Look, I sympathize.
瞧，我深表同情。
He's gotta work here
until he pays off his tab.
他必须在这里工作
直到他还清账单。
- I've got some money.
- I'll contribute to that.
- 我有一些钱。
- 我会为此做出贡献。
What? That's not...
I didn't really... oh... oh.
什么？那不是...
我真的没有……哦……哦。
[gasps]
[overlapping complaints]
[喘气]
[重叠投诉]
Just get that menace
out of here!
只是受到那个威胁
离开这里！
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[grumbling]
Hmm?
[抱怨]
嗯？
All right, Bubble Bass.
Your tab's been wiped clean.
好吧，泡泡巴斯。
你的标签已经被擦干净了。
You can go.
你可以走了。
Well?
Go already!
出色地？
已经走了！
Verily, I am free-ith.
确实，我是自由的。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
[cash register dings]
Huh?
[收银机叮叮声]
嗯？
[laughs]
[笑]
[whinnies]
Krabs!
[嘶嘶声]
螃蟹们！
I thank thee,
clapper-clawed barnacle,
我感谢你，
拍手藤壶，
for forgiving my debt, and FYI,
免除我的债务，仅供参考，
I just opened up a new tab.
我刚刚打开了一个新标签。
[squeals, cackles]
[尖叫声，咯咯笑声]
Hi-ya!
- [growls]
嗨呀！
- [咆哮]
Oh, Bubble Bass!
哦，泡泡鲈鱼！
[laughs]
[笑]
Olé, Señor Squidward?
奥莱，章鱼哥先生？
Olé, SpongeBob.
奥莱，海绵宝宝。
[both humming]
[两人都哼哼]
I'll lead.
我来领导。
- May I?
- Hmm?
- 我可以？
- 唔？
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Eh, but, of course.
呃，但是，当然。
[both humming]
[两人都哼哼]